(Sun Honglei)
(Li Naiwen)
(Guo Jingfei)
(Liu Yuning)
(Gong Jun)
(Chen Xingxu)
(Wang Yuwen)
(Lin Yi)
=Wow The World S2 Extra Episode=
Pick one romantic partner duo
per round
for the tacit guess game.
One player wears headphones
and describes the word,
while the other player guesses the word.
While describing, you must not
use any words from the question.
During the guessing session,
the other six members wear blindfolds
and catch this pair inside the venue.
If either member is caught,
eliminate the whole pair right now.
During this process,
the catchers can also buzz in
based on the description.
A correct buzz-in answer
will void the current word right away.
The guesser gets no points
for this question.
Each pair gets six questions in total.
The winner is the pair
with more correct answers in the end.
Now, let's try a practice round.
(Topic: Iron-Crutch Li)
Come on, get ready.
(Iron-Crutch Li)
Fei's clothes are making too much noise.
- Just target Fei.
- Everyone, put on your blindfolds.
Three, two, one, go!
One of the Eight Immortals.
(Danger
Hands ready)
(Claws are already attached)
One of the Eight Immortals.
Iron-Crutch Li.
Lv Dongbin.
Got him! I got him!
Got him!
(Shocked)
That was too fast.
- Iron-Crutch Li. You got it right.
- Yes.
One point.
He got it right?
Correct.
I got it right straight away, didn't I?
How did you let them catch you then?
I said Iron-Crutch Li.
I was grabbed right when I said "Li".
You should say it in a safe place.
I was thinking of
the other seven Immortals.
So I forgot to run.
(Brain system loading error)
His brain can only handle one thing
at a time.
You lost because of your outfit, Fei.
No sense of accomplishment at all.
(Second pair: Lin Yi, Wang Yuwen)
Everyone else, put your blindfolds on.
Come on.
(Arc de Triomphe)
Lin Yi is easy to catch.
Are you sure?
Not necessarily.
I'm telling you.
He's like a wild horse running loose.
Let me tell you.
(Carefully)
Don't let Lin Yi step on you.
His soles are really thick.
Three, two, one, go!
Who?
Me.
I heard...
I heard the sound from the headphones.
Who is this?
- Me.
- Okay.
(Now is the time!)
Don't talk.
Keep quiet, everyone.
(Your teammate is here)
(I'm coming)
The gate that welcomed Napoleon.
Got him.
(Buzz in at light speed)
Arc de Triomphe.
(A belated arrival)
(Run)
- Who is this?
- It's me.
Correct.
Got one question right.
I answered it.
(Go find my teammate quickly)
(Digestive tablets)
When you overeat and can't digest well.
(Digestive tablets?)
Digestive tablets.
Correct.
What? How is that correct?
(Lv Dongbin)
Who is this?
Me.
Someone punched me.
(Walking straight over)
(Make a run for it right now)
I...
(Wish everyone a happy New Year
in advance)
The one the dog bit.
Lv Dongbin.
Correct.
(Rose jam)
A sauce made from a kind of flower
native to Yunnan.
Rose sauce.
(Following along)
(We're set)
(Oh, no)
What sauce?
Mushroom sauce.
From Yunnan.
What sauce?
Isn't "mushroom sauce" three words?
Matsutake sauce.
Curry sauce.
Chili sauce.
(The train of thought
is totally off track)
The first two words
stand for a type of flower.
(Grab the key points)
The first word is "flower".
Flower mushroom.
I got her.
Got one!
The third word.
Come on. Everyone, stop!
What is it?
Rose jam.
Yuning's team got one point.
You got two points.
Everyone else, put your blindfolds on.
How am I supposed to know when I start?
I'll tell you.
It's useless.
It hasn't started yet.
(No cheating)
Three, two, one, go!
(Buddha Jumps Over the Wall)
Behind a temple,
a fragrant delicacy.
(What sound?)
Three words.
Something extremely fragrant being
cooked in the backyard of a temple.
Three words.
Something very savory.
Soup cube.
Mushroom sauce.
It has meat, seafood, and shark fin.
Temple?
Three words.
The second word.
(Jump)
- Something very delicious.
- Something savory.
Old chicken soup.
Big oysters.
Buddha Jumps Over the Wall.
Correct.
Okay, fine.
Impressive, nice work.
(Topic: Secret)
A foreign classic.
A man and a woman eloped together.
Four words.
A man and a woman.
Midnight in Paris.
Got you!
Everyone, take off your blindfolds.
A man and a woman eloped together.
Why do you grab me?
Have Qian repeat her description
and everyone guess along, okay?
Come on, say it.
A foreign classic.
A man and a woman eloped together.
Pride and Prejudice.
Romeo and Juliet.
Seven words.
He got it right.
- Romeo and Juliet.
Okay.
- How many points did we get?
- Zero points?
One point.
One point is not bad at all.
You even guessed
Buddha Jumps Over the Wall.
Actually, it's quite hard.
Because once you put on headphones,
your voice gets amplified naturally.
- Xingxu guessed it.
- Xingxu shouted it out.
Yes, Xingxu.
Xingxu, you are
on their team.
Honglei, put on the headphones.
Everyone else, put your blindfolds on.
Ready, three, two, one.
(Lao Gan Ma)
Just now,
was someone teasing me?
Me.
Then who just hit me?
(Believed it for real)
We're catching you.
Not me.
(It got out of hand)
(Almost)
Who?
Nai.
(As smooth as a loach)
(Trying to get attention)
(Three words)
(Received successfully)
Sichuan spicy sauce.
What?
Doubanjiang.
- Wrong.
- Doubanjiang.
How many words?
Lao Gan Ma.
Correct.
Start.
(Hold all the power)
(Four words)
Idiom.
Nvwa Mends the Sky.
Hou Yi Shoots the Suns.
Jingwei Fills the Sea.
Who?
Me.
Why are you pulling me?
I'm exhausted.
Me.
(Exhausted)
Who are you?
(Not enough words,
sign language fills in the gaps)
Hold all the power.
Correct.
Okay, got one point.
(Nai is worn out)
Nai has given up.
Game over.
(Not really
The Drunken Concubine)
It's me.
You.
A play.
Written by?
Come on.
Come on, grab him.
Grab him.
(Sun Honglei is caught)
(Already given up struggling)
Was the previous one correct?
Yes.
Born of the same root,
why burn each other so hotly?
It sounded like
they were fighting over there,
like a group fight.
So scary.
The next game
has a little to do with acting.
(Acting Relay)
Next,
split everyone into two teams
of three.
Two members act out clues,
and one acts as the guide.
The guide has to get the actors
to say three preset lines.
Once all three are guessed correctly,
they also need to figure out
the final improvised line
from the other team.
The team with the shortest time wins.
Let's do a trial round first.
Come on.
(Scenario: A killer duo secretly plots on the street
to eliminate their boss, who unexpectedly shows up)
(Getting interested)
This is good.
I think this is fun.
This is quite interesting.
We can totally pull this off.
You're good at spy dramas, right?
Spy.
You're good at it too.
How about we...
(You're not on the same team)
- The three of us. - Let's do this.
I'm the boss.
Okay.
Three, two, one.
Start.
(Scenario: A killer duo secretly plots on the street
to eliminate their boss, who unexpectedly shows up)
(Chen Xingxu plays the apprentice)
Nai.
(Li Naiwen plays the master)
How did you get there?
(Role-play only, no real feelings)
How come you have time today?
I've been waiting for you for ages.
Really?
You have no idea
what happened yesterday.
I met a really tough client.
Come on, you're a total veteran.
- Right?
- No.
Xingxu, let me tell you.
I've decided
to retire.
No.
I don't want to do this anymore.
Okay, but...
I'm hanging up my blades.
(Is this the plot?)
From now on,
all missions,
tough
or easy,
go to you.
You earn the money yourself.
Master.
Okay?
Yes, that's right.
You taught me that
the top rule
is always to get away
completely unscathed, right?
- Right.
- Sticking it out till the end
- never ends well.
- Exactly.
- But you're putting me in a tough spot.
- A man who often walks by the river
will inevitably
get his shoes wet.
You know?
Wait a minute.
How did I just get a message?
Look.
Master.
I kept saying I wanted to retire.
How come I got assigned another mission?
So tell me, should I retire or not?
Go back.
Turn back.
Then you...
Did you
get a mission too?
Master,
considering all the years
you've mentored me,
I'll tell you the truth.
Okay.
Stop while you still can.
Song Qian says...
Wait.
Song Qian?
Boss.
Is Song Qian texting you directly?
Then what did the message
she sent me earlier
even mean?
Wait.
Let me sort this out.
The message she sent me...
Her mission for me is to...
Here's the thing, Xingxu.
Actually,
I got a message too.
She ordered me to kill you.
How can I believe you?
It's true.
How about you?
She ordered me to kill you.
See?
Why?
(Already immersed in the plot)
Xingxu.
We're brothers
through and through.
Yes.
Right?
What gives her the right
to make you kill me,
or make me kill you?
She definitely wants one of us to die.
Right.
Right?
Mutually...
Do you think this plan works?
Definitely not.
Then what should we do?
Take her out.
We have to take her out.
(Now it's my turn to go on stage)
(Lines: Mole, torture, Morse code)
(Song Qian plays the boss)
Boss.
The boss is here.
I received a telegram this afternoon.
Yes.
Someone wants to take me out.
- Impossible.
Absolutely impossible.
So I suspect that in our agency,
there is...
What agency?
Daycare center?
Research institute?
Which agency are you talking about?
It is not important.
The key point is that in our agency...
In our agency.
Think it over carefully.
In our agency,
there are Northeast people.
There are Northeast people.
Cut the chatter.
Sorry.
So I thought of something.
In our agency,
there are...
four words?
Two words.
(Extremely close to the right answer)
Undercover?
He's not...
Mole.
Then who is it?
Who's the mole?
Xingxu, do you think it's me?
I don't think so.
I don't think it's you either.
Right?
Yes.
It must be someone else.
Come on.
You two.
Come over here.
You two
are my best sidekicks all along.
- Yes.
- Of course.
In our agency,
anyone who makes a mistake
We won't let them off easily.
Right.
For example,
drinking a bowl of chili water
on an empty stomach.
Empty stomach?
That's really bad for the stomach.
Using hot pot base
as toothpaste to brush their teeth.
(The comic duo)
So cruel?
These are our bureau's
cruelest
- punishments.
- Torture.
(Impressive)
That's too harsh.
He's really good at guessing.
This is unbearable, right?
But...
So, what do you two think
we should deal with the mole
when we find out who they are?
Brush their teeth with chili water.
Use hot pot base.
How do you want to punish him?
What do you think?
We'll follow your lead.
Today,
I received a secret report.
In our bureau,
there's a Three Character Classic...
We're so cultured.
Seriously.
Someone hid some secrets in it.
Yes.
What secrets?
People at birth are naturally good.
Their natures are similar,
but habits make them differ.
It's like,
When you go out, on the bureau's door,
knock...
If a kid is not taught...
Knock.
Two long, four short.
(I did my best)
Two long...
And there are different fingerprints.
Morse code.
They used Morse code to send a message.
Yes.
(So fast?)
What?
(Secret)
Good.
(Ultimate line)
A telegram is coming.
(Your secret message has been delivered)
Another secret message.
Nai, you stepped on it.
Oh no.
The message.
It's this person.
This person suddenly sent a message.
A Pigeon Post.
Who exactly sent you this?
Boss, I'll read it first.
Read it.
Okay.
(Secret)
(Ultimate line: Secret.)
No problem, boss, trust me.
How is it?
Which side sent you the message?
(Getting into the character)
Boss, here's the thing.
Now,
our missions
are getting more and more complex.
Covering a wide range, right?
Now, including some bosses,
and their families,
and more detailed intel,
we need to know all those.
Like parents
or children.
Right now, I think children's intel
is the hardest to get.
(Grasp the keyword: related to children)
So we need to...
I need to constantly watch them.
Naiwen, do you know what it is?
I know.
Watch them.
For example, what books they read?
Yes.
And the TV shows they watches.
Especially those things kids love.
It's like...
Comics?
For kids?
There are comics.
On TV, there are also some...
Cartoons.
(Another keyword: Cartoons)
Cartoons, yes.
One of the cartoons...
Peppa Pig?
No.
I was using binoculars to watch it.
You used binoculars to watch
- the comic?
- I watched the cartoon.
Have you seen that cartoon?
I haven't.
But I only saw its title.
The title.
Title.
(Key info: Three words)
Yes, just three words.
A three-word title.
Journey to the West?
Cartoon.
The animated version
of Journey to the West?
No.
The ink-wash version?
I haven't even seen it.
Could someone my age
possibly never watch
Journey to the West?
(Seems reasonable)
Well,
then just describe
this...
- He hasn't even seen it.
- Yes, describe it.
Describe its title.
You've seen this title, right?
You acted bravely for a just cause once,
right?
- Yes.
- Right?
On the bus,
you spotted a thief.
Yes.
- You caught him on the spot.
- Caught him.
Then, you sent him to...
P...
(Ultimate line: Patrick Star)
Patrick Star?
(Four minutes ago)
Patrick Star.
Good.
There's actually Patrick Star on this.
(Impressive)
Xingxu, good job.
Good.
So, your intel includes Patrick Star?
I don't...
So, it's Patrick Star
who wants to murder me?
How do you know that Patrick Star
is actually someone's code name.
How do you know it's a code name?
(Boss, let me explain)
Are you Patrick Star?
You guessed right.
I am Patrick Star.
Otherwise,
how would you know Patrick Star?
So, Patrick Star is you.
I only know I have a mission.
I have a signal.
Xingxu, use your brain, quickly!
SpongeBob, let's go catch jellyfish!
Good.
Your spent
14 minutes and 54 seconds.
Come on, next team.
(Scenario)
(Husband and wife or Father and son)
A couple goes to the hospital.
The doctor has a grave expression.
Just this one line.
A couple goes to the hospital.
The doctor has a grave expression.
Does anyone want to volunteer
for a role?
What do you want to play, bro?
Version one, version two.
Yes, father and son or husband and wife.
I think the couple is more interesting.
Definitely, the couple is more fun.
Let's do this.
I think the fun is this,
you play the attending doctor, okay?
You be the attending doctor.
You the wife, you the husband.
Let's do it, okay?
Alright.
This is fun.
I'll guide.
- Guide.
- Guiding requires fast thinking.
Okay, no problem.
Come on, you go.
Alright.
Okay, three,
two, one,
Go.
(A couple goes to the hospital.
The doctor looks serious.)
(Sun Honglei as the husband)
Honglei,
(Wang Yuwen plays the wife)
(Scenario acting)
I'm feeling anxious.
Don't be,
Why are you anxious?
I'm afraid the results won't be good.
Listen to the doctor.
(Lin Yi plays the attending doctor)
Let's go inside.
You go first.
I'm a bit anxious.
(Hard to stay serious)
You told me not to worry,
but you're the most worried one.
No matter what the final result is,
I'll be with you.
If it's really a serious illness,
will you abandon me?
I won't, Honglei.
No matter what, I'll be with you.
Do you love me?
Of course, I love you.
I love you too.
Why are you testing my sincerity
at a time like this?
Alright.
Let's go in first.
Come in.
You're here.
I've been waiting for ages.
Have a seat.
Sit down.
Not a bit of chivalry.
How annoying!
Move.
Positioning.
Did you take the medicine
prescribed last time?
- Yes.
- On time?
Yes.
This medicine was for him, right?
Who took it?
We both took some.
- You both took some?
- We both took it.
It takes two to tango.
You both have some issues.
We both have issues?
(Line: The envy of others. Perfect couple.)
Years married?
(Shivering all over)
We're married for a few years.
A few years.
(Silence)
Your wife is so smart.
You seem
to be living a good life.
Is that related?
So smart,
and you can tell their life is good?
So forced.
(I have my own pace)
Good life.
To parents,
kids from other families are better.
A couple from another family...
So envious.
The envy of others.
(Quite in sync)
Correct?
In other people's words, you are...
A perfect couple.
We're still acting.
(Accidentally broke character)
No need to get so excited.
That's great.
I'm happy for you two.
(Smoothly got back into character)
Happy for you two.
(Click tongue)
(The vibe suddenly changed)
What's wrong with us now?
The vibe changed suddenly, why?
(Let me think)
Didn't you say you needed to recuperate?
Recuperate.
Doctor, you mean...
How many characters?
Four.
- Four characters.
I remember back then she was...
Cold.
Didn't you say she was cold?
Always say four-character phrases.
I don't have
much cultural knowledge.
I just very superficially
described this.
Cold.
Cold means...
Soreness and back pain?
Cold.
(Ran out of words)
She was so cold she was shivering.
Shivering.
Trembling.
(Very close)
Not just one area.
Not just one area?
Is the word "cold" included?
Almost.
It's a symptom.
Symptom.
Not really a symptom.
A kind of...
Manifestation.
(Hard to stay serious)
- Like it's turning into winter.
- Cold.
Cold.
Cold as ice.
I'm very superficial.
I am under-educated.
Under-educated?
Don't think about idioms.
Cold wind?
That's too romantic.
Ice cold.
It's cold everywhere.
From head to toe.
A world of ice and snow.
Bitterly cold.
He's uneducated.
Just cold.
Cold.
(Who on earth is called "Cold"?)
At this moment,
you feel
someone turn on the air conditioner.
I'm so cold.
The cold is piercing.
Why is it so cold?
I'll just put it this way.
The first word you told me back then.
What?
I'll tell you,
this
water, you,
better stay away.
This muddy water?
The first word,
didn't you say that to me?
Freezing all over?
No.
You, on New Year,
at that supermarket, didn't they...
(at a loss for words)
Well...
What about the supermarket?
What about the eggs?
Giving out eggs.
Shivering all over?
Shivering.
Cold.
Cold all over?
Are these the four words?
Yes.
(Unbelievable)
Doctor, such a simple phrase?
(Embarrassed)
It was really simple, right?
(Here comes the hard part)
(Discussing the ultimate lines)
(Great truths are simple)
(Ultimate line: Great truths are simple)
(I have a bad feeling)
You can do it, Honglei.
It's okay, Honglei.
Dr. Lin.
You've been talking for so long.
I want to, on behalf of my wife,
say a couple of words to you.
I just want to say four characters.
Always four characters.
(I think I've seen this before)
Let's just say something simple.
Okay?
Okay.
Just tell the two of us
how should we live our life.
You don't need to beat around the bush.
All roads
lead to where?
Rome.
(Why was there a trivia quiz?)
Actually, in life...
(I really can't make it up anymore)
(Think)
I found...
Look, you keept
talking about it,
but actually,
"cold all over"
can be expressed differently.
You can simply,
the simplest way,
sum up in four characters.
What are the four characters?
Concise and comprehensive.
That should be
Suddenly look back.
Don't distract us.
A big road,
how do you cross it?
No need to detour.
Right?
Dear, you still don't understand?
I don't,
(Honest.)
These four words are
- Are they cultured words?
- from the Chinese culture.
For example,
the highest goodness is like water.
The highest goodness is like water.
Excelling in both virtue and art.
It has something to do with the road.
What about Heaven rewards the diligent?
The second word is already correct.
Great truths are simple.
This is good.
Dr. Lin,
I know you are a philosopher.
Philosopher?
You made such a simple thing
so complicated.
I think you had a point.
Great truths are simple.
For you, great truths are complicated.
- Good.
- Okay.
Thank you, Doctor.
How many minutes?
You took 14 minutes.
That was fun.
This is fun.
Not bad.